麦琪:不,你吓到小宝宝了,杰森,你没听见我叫你.
Maggie: No, you are frightening the baby, Jason.I have not known the call.
杰森:麦琪?
Jason: Maggie?
麦琪:杰森,现在太晚了,我已经擦过背了.
Maggie: Too late, Jason.I already scrubbed my own back.
杰森:不,现在是几点?
Jason: No, what time it is?
摄影师:嘿!
Cameraman: Hi.
杰森:嘿!
Jason: Hi.
摄影师:现在我们再来一次,这次你要表现的迷惑一点.好了吗?五秒准备,四三二开始.
Cameraman: We are going to do this again.This time, we really need to believe you are confusing.All right?Five seconds... four... three... two... and...action.
杰森:他是谁?为什么他们会在浴室拍电视?
Jason: Who is that?Why are these TV cameras doing in our bathroom?
麦琪:哦,这感觉真好!
Maggie: Oh, I feel so good.
杰森:亲爱的,你并没有怀孕.
Jason: Honey, you are not pregnant.
麦琪:当然我没有怀孕.
Maggie: Of course, I am not pregnant.
杰森:可是昨晚你为什么说你怀孕四个月了?
Jason: Why you said last night that you've been pregnant for the last
four months?
麦琪:对不起,亲爱的,你挡到我的镜头了.
Maggie: Excuse me, Honey, you block my shot.
杰森:亲爱的,你已经怀孕四个月了.可是怎么现在冲了个澡之后就没有了呢?
Jason: Honey, you are pregnant for 4 months, then once you stepped in the shower, now
you are not
麦琪:哦,杰森,那只是你想的
Maggie: Oh, Jason, you must have dreamed all that.
杰森:不可能,亲爱的,这样的事只可能发生在那些蹩脚的电视剧里.
Jason: It couldn't be, honey, that only happens on TV.Bad television.
麦琪:你明白我在演播室工作,要是想不要被解雇,
Maggie: Look at this.I am to tell the television studio.
我就不能化太多的时间在孩子身上.
I want that here to fired I don't care how much kid is supporting.
麦琪:杰森,杰森!
Maggie: Jason, Jason.
杰森:什么?什么?
Jason: What?What?
麦琪:现在看着我!
Maggie: Look at me.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:你瞧!我怀孕了!
Maggie: Look, I am pregnant.
杰森:我知道,到时我会在你身边的.
Jason: I know.I was there where it happened.
麦琪:哦,我梦想这样.
Maggie: Oh It's a dream.
杰森:谢谢!
Jason: Thank you.
麦琪:我刚才的梦可不是这样.
Maggie: Not that what I dreamed.
杰森:哦,你刚刚都梦见了什么?
Jason: Oh, what did you dream?
麦琪:我刚刚冲澡完了出来,突然发现自己没有怀孕了.
Maggie: I stepped out of the shower, and suddenly, I was not pregnant.
已经有是个月的身孕突然一下没有啦!
Everything that happened for the last 4 months has been changed.
杰森:那只可能在电视剧中会发生.
Jason: That only happens on Television.
杰森:而且是蹩脚的电视剧
Jason: Bad TV.
麦琪:你没必要这样说我吧!
Maggie: Not necessarily.
杰森:我想你的梦是说明你对怀孕有一种复杂的情绪.
Jason: Well, I think your dream could mean your have a mixed emotion about
being pregnant.
麦琪:哦,杰森,我们就要有另一个孩子啦!
Maggie: Oh, Jason, I am thrilled about having another baby, I am happy,
我是如此激动!如此开心!如此骄傲!
I am proud.I want the whole world to know.
我真想告诉全世界,你难道看不出我怀孕了?是不是?
Cannot tell I am pregnant, can you?
杰森:我看不出.
Jason: I can tell you are.
麦琪:你不想再要一个孩子吗?
Maggie: So you hate it
杰森:不,不!当然很好.
Jason: No.no.I know, it's nice.
麦琪:你在说谎!
Maggie: You are lying.
杰森:你说你要去买些孕妇装.
Jason: You said that you were going to look maternity clothes.
麦琪:杰森,你叫我怎么去买孕妇装,
Maggie: Jason, how could I buy maternity clothes,
工作和家务让我根本抽不出时间来.
I have no time between work and home and keeping the nursery ready.
杰森:你老板有没有让你在孩子出生前减轻工作量呢?
Jason: And When your boss can let you slow down a little bit?After the baby is born?
麦琪:这……
Maggie: Well...
杰森:你告诉他你怀孕的时候,他是什么反应?
Jason: What did he say when you told him you were pregnant?
麦琪:没有说什么!真的.
Maggie: Not that much really.
杰森:啊?
Jason: Aha?
麦琪:啊是什么意思?
Maggie: Aha what?
杰森:你是还没有告诉他,对吧?
Jason: You still haven't even told him, have you?
麦琪:杰森,你以为你就很了解我.
Maggie: Jason, you think you know me so well.
杰森:是的,我很了解你.
Jason: Yes, I do.
麦琪:好吧!现在还不是告诉他的时候.
Maggie: Ok, it's just not been the right time now.
杰森:出了事就晚了,下星期你还要拍特技飞行系列片.
Jason: It will take a wrong time next week when you are late when you do your aerobics
麦琪:这不是在我穿孕妇装之后吗?
Maggie: Before I wear something baggy?
杰森:亲爱的,我只是……
Jason: Honey, I just...
麦琪:你知道我的想法的,
Maggie: You know what I think.
我想你对我的怀孕有些不安.
I think you are the one who is uncomfortable with my being pregnant.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:要不然你怎么解释你的梦?
Maggie: How well do you explain your dream?
杰森:那是你在做梦.
Jason: It was your dream.
麦琪:哦……
Maggie: Oh...
杰森:麦琪,我想你还是越早告诉你的老板越好.
Jason: Maggie, I think the sooner you tell your boss you have the baby, the better.
麦琪:你讲得对.
Maggie: You are right.
杰森:太好了.
Jason: Good.
麦琪:明天我就告诉他.
Maggie: I will definitely tell him today.
杰森:那才是我的好老婆.
Jason: That's my girl.
麦琪:前提是我能见得到他.
Maggie: If I see him.
杰森:哦……
Jason: Oh...
本:真是太棒了,我们放假一天,
Ben: Boy, this is great; we get a whole school day off.
我真喜欢老师开会.
I love teachers' conferences.
迈克:要是有更多的会就好了.
Mike: We need more of them.
本:你知不知道老师们一天都在谈些什么?
Ben: What do you think teachers talk about all day?
迈克:谈论你,本.
Mike: You, Ben.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
开萝尔:早上好.
Carol: Morning.
迈克:假日还看书?你真是努力!
Mike: School books on the holiday?Even nerds don't do that.
开萝尔:这是本人名书,
Carol: Here is proclamation books of names,
我在为我的新妹妹选名字.
carrying suggestion for my new sister.
迈克:妹妹?你真是在浪费时间,可能会是个男孩.
Mike: Sister?You could waste your time, It could be a boy.
开萝尔:要是男孩的话,就随便你给他取个名,到时我就离家出走.
Carol: If it's a boy, then you can name him whatever you want, then I am leaving home.
迈克:你敢保证吗?
Mike: You promise?
迈克:嘿!本,
Mike: Hey, Ben, Come on.
放松点,刚刚我是跟你在开玩笑,老师们不是在讨论你.
Relax, I was just kidding that not our teachers are talking about you.
开萝尔:真是太棒了,到时就可以给她买些小孩的衣服,再带她出去散步.
Carol: Oh, It is going to be so neat.Just buying her Little clothes, taking
her for walks
迈克:到时吐你一身.
Mike: Have a vomit for you.
本:宝宝也会吐吗?
Ben: Babies do that?
迈克:是的,那是宝宝们最喜欢做的事.
Mike: Yeah, it was the nice things they do.
本:我是婴儿的时候是不是也喜欢吐?
Ben: Did I vomit when I was the baby?
开萝尔:是的,全吐在我身上.
Carol: Yeah, all over me.
迈克:做的好.
Mike: Good Work there.
开萝尔:等等,到时有了小宝宝的话,你俩就得学乖点.
Carol: Just wait, when new baby gets here, you both have to clean up your ax.
迈克:不用担心了.
Mike: Big deal.
开萝尔:到时妈妈不会像保护婴儿一样再帮你了.
Carol: You think it's a big deal when mom can't save you that baby defense
anymore.
本:保护婴儿?
Ben: Baby defense?
麦琪:杰森,你知道他还只是孩子,你不要对他这么凶.
Maggie: You know, Jason, go easy.he is our baby.
迈克:哦,本,你还是面对现实吧!你还是干了不少小孩的蠢事的.
Mike: Oh, Ben, face it.You've done a lot of dun baby things.
开萝尔:再讲我就对你不客气了.
Carol: You change that back.
杰森:本,不要晚吃的东西,你不是小婴儿了.
Jason: Ben, don't play with your food.You are not a baby.
麦琪:你爸爸讲的对,本.
Maggie: Your father is right, Ben.
杰森:你该多喝点牛奶,你有两个人要吃!
Jason: You'd better have more than that, You are eating for two.
迈克:本也是一样!
Mike: So is Ben.
麦琪:谢谢,杰森.
Maggie: Thank you, Jason.
麦琪:再见,孩子们,假日快乐.
Maggie: Bye, kids, enjoy your day-off.
杰森:麦琪,记得今天你要说的事?
Jason: Don't forget today, Maggie?
麦琪:好的,我保证会和老板说的.
Maggie: Yes, I will talk to my boss, I promise.
难道要我写学书吗?抱歉,现在我得走了.
You want me to write it with blood.Sorry, I've got to go.
杰森:好吧,你妈妈有点紧张.
Jason: Well, your mother is feeling a little tense.
迈克:一点点,不过这不会有事的.
Mike: A little, but things are never gone.
杰森:是的,她怀孕了,这样工作过度就更加容易累.
Jason: Well, she is pregnant, tired and over worked.
本:谁不是这样?
Ben: Who is it?
开萝尔:我能理解,是的,妈妈这样的年纪还要生小孩,这的确会有些困难.
Carol: I understand.Well , mom is very difficult to have a baby in the autumn
of her life
杰森:你这话可千万不能跟你妈妈讲!
Jason: Don't you ever, ever, never say that to your mother.
开萝尔:我当然不会讲的.
Carol: Got that.
杰森:首先,
Jason: First of all, what we can do for her and make her feel good.
看看我们做些什么能让她感觉好些的事?她老是担心准备工作做的太晚,
She has been worried lately about getting ready for the baby,
譬如婴儿房布置的太晚.
decorating the nursery room.
开萝尔:爸爸,今天我们就来布置婴儿房吧!
Carol: Dad, that's it.Dad, we can decorate the nursery today.
杰森:这个提议不错.
Jason: That's not bad idea.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Thank you.
本:但是爸爸,我今天还有件大事要做.
Ben: But dad, I have a big stuff to do today.
杰森:你难道不想为你妈妈做些什么吗?
Jason: Wouldn't you like to do something nice for your mother?
本:必须得做吗?
Ben: Do I've choice?
杰森:是的.
Jason: No.
本:好吧!
Ben: Sure.
杰森:你呢?迈克!
Jason: How about you, Mike?
迈克:我本想一天都用来学习功课的,
Mike: Well, actually, I was planning to spend the entire day studying.
不过我愿意帮忙!
I would love to help.
杰森:太好了,我们要把客房装饰成为妈妈从未见过的一流的育婴房.
Jason: Oh, Great.This is we're going to cheer up.We are going to take
the guest room and make it best looking nursery she ever saw
杰森:来吧,我们开始吧!
Jason: Come on, let's go.
杰森:你的提议真是不错,开萝尔.
Jason: Good thinking, Carol.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Thank you.
迈克:的确是个好提议.开萝尔,你真是把我们的一天都毁啦!
Mike: Yeah, Good thinking, Carol.You are nice to ruin the whole day for all
of us
开萝尔:你就是我的目的.
Carol: That was my plan.
杰森:十一,十二.
Jason: Eleven, Twelve.
迈克:怎么啦?
Mike: What's wrong?
杰森:我刚刚忘记客房是在楼下的.
Jason: Well, I never thought of before the guest room is all the way down
the hall.
迈克:那怎样?
Mike: So?
杰森:因为你妈妈和我要离育婴房近些.
Jason: Your mother and I have to be closer to the nursery.
本:好吧,那就去弄另一间客房吧.
Ben: Well, all the other rooms are taken.
杰森:是的,我们得稍微调整一下卧室,
Jason: Oh, what we just might have to is to do some rearranging.
我马上回来.
I'll be right back.
本:重新调整?
Ben: Rearranging?
迈克:哦,不,谁会失去卧室?
Mike: Oh, no.who is going to lose his room?
本:什么?
Ben: What?
开萝尔:迈克,为了宝宝,调整一下也没关系.
Carol: Mike, it matters it's good for the baby.
迈克:那就调整一下你的卧室.
Mike: Then you give up your room.
开萝尔:要是爸爸决定了,我就同意.
Carol: Well, if that's the decision.Then that's the decision.
杰森:开萝尔,你的电话.
Jason: Carol, your telephone.
迈克:本,我们得快点有所行动.
Mike: Ben, look out, we got to move fast here.
本:行动?你是说我们把自己的卧室腾出来?
Ben: Move?You mean we are out?
迈克:不,不!
Mike: No, no, I just mean you've got to make sure you don't want to be
我是说你得想办法不要被赶到客房里.
in the guest room.
本:我怎么回被赶到客房里?
Ben: Why do I want to be in the guest room?
迈克:好了,本,,你想想谁的卧室离爸妈的房间最近?
Mike: Well, think about it, Ben, whose room is close mom and dad?
本:你的.
Ben: Yours.
迈克:是的,但是你我之间的房间,哪个的损坏程度最小?
Mike: Ok, but between the two of us, which has the least physical damage?
本:我的.
Ben: Mine.
迈克:那就对了.
Mike: Right.
本:哦,不.
Ben: Oh, no.
迈克:我敢打赌开萝尔现在正在向爸爸提建议呢!
Mike: I bet Carol is pointing it out to dad right now.
本:我招惹她了吗?
Ben: I didn't mean fun of her?
迈克:我要是你的话,我是怎么也不会住那客房的.
Mike: If it were me,I would do anything to get out of the guest room.
本:我也是的,客房里的墙纸旧简直像外婆一样.
Ben: Me too.Its wallpaper is as old as grandma.
迈克:我想我们最好想些办法出来应付,等等,
Mike: I just wish there is some way we can make sure that...
也许这是一个疯狂的想法.
oh, wait a minute.Oh, nay, it's too crazy.
本:我们就去试试吧,是什么办法?
Ben: Let's do it.What is it?
迈克:好吧!那就是你自愿腾出你的卧室来.
Mike: Ok All right, you volunteer to give up your room.
本:这真是个疯狂的主意.
Ben: It's too crazy.
迈克:不,本,你给我听着.到时爸爸一听到你自愿腾出你的卧室,他一感动就会让你移出任选一间卧室的.
Mike: No, listen, Ben.Dad will be so touched that you offer your room to
baby, then no worry let you pick up any other bedroom in the house
本:到时我就选你的.
Ben: Great I'll take yours.
迈克:好吧,你知道谁的房间最大吗?
Mike: Well, who has the biggest room in the house?
本:爸爸妈妈的.
Ben: Mom and dad.
迈克:好吧,那其次的呢?
Mike: Ok, the second biggest?
本:开萝尔的.
Ben: Carol.
迈克:好了,我知道这并不是最好的做法,但是有了小宝宝这也没办法的.
Mike: Right.I know it's not the great thing to do, Ben.But the baby comes at this times.
杰森:好了,现在改哪间?
Jason: Ok where we worry.
本:爸爸,就让宝宝用我的房间吧!
Ben: Dad, I want the baby to have my room.
杰森:哦,本,你真是无私!你真令我感动!
Jason: Oh, that's very unselfish, Ben, I am touched.
本:我只是想让宝宝住最好的地方.
Ben: I just want whatever best for the baby.
杰森:你是自愿的吗?
Jason: You mean that?
本:老实说吗?
Ben: Cross my heart?
杰森:你和迈克的房间里我们的卧室都很近,我想你们还是投硬币决定.
Jason: You know your room and Mike's are both so close, it's going to be
a tarsar
本:可以吗?
Ben: It was?
杰森:是的,这是因为你的慷慨大方让我才做这样的决定的
Jason: Yes.It's because of your generosity Ben, that makes a decision easy for me.
杰森:我保证只要育婴房一弄好,我就帮你去整理你的新房间.
Jason: I want you know as soon as I finished the baby room, then to
work against things room for you.Ok
迈克:对不起,本,我们的差一点就成功了.
Mike: Sorry, Ben, we tried.So close.
麦琪:德尔玛,西德通完电话的时候,你能告诉我一下吗?
Maggie: Delmar, would you tell me the minute when Mr.Sid is just off the phone?
德尔玛:哦,好的,我想会很很快的.他只是在问肖娜产假结束后什么时候来上班?
Delmar: Oh, yeah, I won't be long.He is just talking with Shoner about when
she comes back from maternity leave
麦琪:哦,她的宝宝还好吗?
Maggie: Oh.How is her baby?
德尔玛:肖娜说她的宝宝晚上终于能安稳的睡到天亮了.你确定你也好要再生一次.
Delmar: Shorner said it's finally sleeping through the night.You're sure you will go through all that again.
麦琪:当然,这很有意思的,你知道我怀孕了?
Maggie: Definitely, it is all born.You know?
德尔玛:当然知道.你跟肖娜那时一模一样,也是穿着孕妇装,没五分钟就会跑趟厕所,在我一提到小孩时就会宝宝这宝宝那的.另外你也是急着找西德谈话.
Delmar: Of course I know.That's Shorner all over again, wearing baggy clothes, running to the bathroom every 5 minutes, saying oh every time I mention babies.Freaking out all about to tell Sid.
麦琪:我可没急着找他,我只是在等一个合适的时间,
Maggie: I am not freaking.I was just waiting for the right time.
现在是不是合适的时间?
This is the right time?
德尔玛:那时当肖娜告诉他的时候,他真是太激动了.
Delmar: When Shorner have told him about the baby, he is thrilling.
麦琪:真的吗?
Maggie: Really?
德尔玛:麦琪,他也是个有小孩的父亲,只是他的事业心太强了.
Delmar: Maggie, he is a family man himself.He is pushy.
麦琪:西德先生,我想占用你一点时间.
Maggie: Mr.Sid, I just save one moment of your time.
西德:哦,麦琪,再等等.
Sid: Oh, Maggie, Wait a second.
西德:德尔玛,给我发一份通知:肖娜·丝玛最近都不能回到十九频道工作,
Sid: Delmor, Send out a memo:
她得在家照顾小宝宝,我想你们不会相信她的鬼话的.
Shorner Smar will not be turning to the Channel 19 anchor desk and having
实际上,
to stay at home with her new baby if you can believe that garbage.
从今以后,在十九频道工作的女士要是怀孕了的话,
In fact, immediately if any woman who works at Channel 19 and gets pregnant
就将被解雇,署名是你们亲爱的西德尔维奇.
will be fired.Signed Sid Sidlevich.
德尔玛:先生,你怎么那样做.
Delmar: Sir, you cannot do that.
西德:我不想那样做,我只是发发牢骚.
Sid: I don't want to do that.I just wanted to say it.
麦琪,你找我有什么事吗?
Well, Maggie, what did you want to see me about?
麦琪:哦,我只是想对你说,祝你快乐!
Maggie: Oh I just wanted to say "have a nice day"!
德尔玛:她的嘴甜吧?
Delmar: Is she sweet?
杰森:好的,伙计们,你们做的不错.等这边的事都做完了,你们把这些油漆灌扔到车库里去.不知道你们妈妈看到这一切会有什么反应?她肯定很高兴,也许会像个小孩一样苦起来的.
Jason: All right, guys.Great job.Please bring these paint cans over to the garage
when you finish.What's the reaction of your mother when she sees this?She is
going to be so happy; she is going to cry like a baby
迈克:你是不是决定不再和我讲话了?
Mike: So, you are never going to talk with me?
本:是的.
Ben: Never.
本:你这不是和我说了吗?
Mike: You just said.
本:从此现在开始.
Ben: Stopping now.
迈克:你又和我说了.
Mike: You did it again.
本:别说了,迈克.
Ben: Stopping, Mike.
迈克:得了吧,本.你看我一直在教你,我想让你学会如何保护自己,因为你在家里的地位已经被小宝宝取代了.
Mike: Come on, look Ben.I said what I've done to you valuable, learning look
out yourself, when your place has been replaced by the new baby in the family
本:我会告诉爸爸的.
Ben: I will tell Dad.
开萝尔:告诉爸爸什么?
Carol: Tell Dad what?
迈克:哦,没什么!他失去了他的……
Mike: Er, nothing, nothing.He is losing his ...
本:迈克说要是我把卧室让给小宝宝的话,爸爸就会把你的卧室让给我.
Ben: Mike said if I gave up my room to the baby, Dad will be keeping yours.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
本:是的,他正……(他们开始争吵)
Ben: Well, he is... (They are quarreling)
杰森:等等,不管你们有什么事都先等会,你们妈妈现在回来啦!到时她已到这里我们就大声惊叫,知道了吗?
Jason: Wait, wait, wait, hold on....whatever this is about, we must wait.Your mother is on the way upstairs.When she gets here, we are yelling surprise.Ok?
麦琪:杰森?
Maggie: Jason?
杰森:是的,我们都在本的房间里.
Jason: Yes, we all happens in Ben's room.
本:现在不是本的了.
Ben: Not anymore.
开萝尔,本,迈克,杰森:大吃一惊吧!
Carol, Ben, Mike, Jason: Surprise!
本:是的,是的!
Ben: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
麦琪:这都是你一个人做的?
Maggie: You did all this?
杰森:不是的,使我和孩子们一起做的.
Jason: Yeah, no, no, just not myself with everybody.
麦琪:大家一起,除了我?
Maggie: Everybody, except me?
杰森:亲爱的,怎么了?
Jason: Honey?
迈克:看来她很喜欢.
Mike: She loves it.
杰森:我现在就不太明白了,我原以为我们为准备育婴房,
Jason: I just don't get it.
你会高兴的.
I think you were so pleased we fixed up the nursery.
麦琪:哦,杰森,
Maggie: Oh, It was a nice gesture, Jason.Even with the hideous drapes.
你们真是做的不错.即便这窗帘不太好看,
What kind of mother am I going to be if I don't even have time to
一个连准备育婴房的时间都没有的妈妈,怎么会是个好妈妈呢?
take part in getting the nursery ready?
杰森:你很好呀!亲爱的,
Jason: You are great one, honey, a sensational one.
你是一个情感丰富的人,只是你没时间管窗帘的事.
Just doesn't have any taste in drapes.
麦琪:一个好妈妈应该要告诉她的老板她怀孕的事.
Maggie: A great mother would've been able to tell her boss she was pregnant.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:我不敢说.
Maggie: I chickened out.
杰森:亲爱的,你怎么就这么害怕告诉他呢?
Jason: Honey, why are you so afraid to tell him?
麦琪:我不是害怕,我知道为什么,我只是担心.
Maggie: I am not afraid.I know what it is.I am just scared.
杰森:那你又是在担心什么?
Jason: Why are you so so scared about?
麦琪:我不知道,到时他会把我当成孕妇,
Maggie: I don't know.That he will treat me like I am pregnant.
这样工作也会发生变化的.
Things are going to change.
杰森:当然,工作是会发生变化的.
Jason: Of course, things are going to change.
麦琪:但我不想工作有所变化,我现在很适应这份工作,
Maggie: But I don't want any change.
我还想做一番大事呢!
I am finally fitting the work and doing a great job.
杰森:亲爱的,我们该面对现实了,
Jason: Oh sweet heart.We just have to face it.
我们需要有所变化.
We are going to make adjustments.
麦琪:什么变化?
Maggie: What adjustments?
杰森:例如我也该减少我的就诊人数.
Jason: Well, like I will reduce my patients low.
麦琪:你会那样做吗?
Maggie: Can you do that?
杰森:当然,我会的.
Jason: Of course I can.I just have to cure those nuts Jason fans.
我会尽快治好那些依赖杰森的人,好了,这只是个笑话.
Well, it's a joke, honey.
麦琪:但是我们以前可从没有谈过你的减少病人就诊量的问题.
Maggie: But we never talked about your scaling down your practice before.
杰森:那是因为以前我从没想过.
Jason: I just never thought of it before.
麦琪:你以前难道就不能想一想吗?
Maggie: Shouldn't you have thought of it before?
杰森:我想这我也不清楚.
Jason: I guess, I don't know.
麦琪:这太好了,看来这孩子注定没前途了,
Maggie: Oh, great.This kid doesn't have a chance.
因为他的母亲是这样不尽职,父亲又是这样没脑子.
She gets a terrible mother and a thought-joked father.
迈克:得了,本,我承认我们的计划实施效果并不理想.
Mike: All right, Ben.I admitted our plan didn't work out perfectly.
本:哦,那是当然.
Ben: Oh, sure it did.
迈克:好了,本,我又想到了一个好主意,这个办法能让开萝尔失去她的卧室.
Mike: Come on, Ben, I have the best motifs ear.I want carol to get
the short in the stake
开萝尔:本,你听迈克的话有什么下场.你要在客房里过日子,每天你都是客人.哦,你都可以把房子租出去了.
Carol: Ben, see what happens when you trust Mike.You end up in the guest
room.A guest in your own home.Oh, boy, my soul, you can rent an
apartment to something
本:开萝尔,你的建议不错.
Ben: Not bad, Carol, not bad.
开萝尔:要是让爸妈知道这件事,我想他们会……,
Carol: And if Mom and dad found out about this, I promise you they will....
到时你的麻烦大啦!
you will be in deep deep trouble.
迈克:别这样,不要把本的住房问题都怪在我头上.
Mike: Look, don't start to blame Ben's housing problems on me.
开萝尔:不这样的话,那又是谁的错?
Carol: Then who is fault with it?
迈克:我想我们都知道是谁!
Mike: I think we both move it that way.
开萝尔:你现在难道想把责任都推倒一个还未出生的孩子身上?
Carol: You are blaming this on the unborn child?
迈克:开萝尔,让我们看看实际情况吧!
Mike: Let's look at the fact, Carol.
现在还不知道这孩子是男是女呢,就已经这么烦了.
I mean, so far this kid I even don't know yet.As sold Everybody.
估计也肯定是个女孩啦!
It is going to be a girl.
开萝尔:迈克,我会为你祈求的.
Carol: Mike, I'll pray for you.
迈克:好了,开萝尔,
Mike: Look, Carol, I mean nobody bothered to ask me how I feel about having
现在也没有人来问我对家中增加一个孩子有什么看法!
a kid around this house.
开萝尔:那也没有人来问我和本呀!
Carol: So, nobody bothered to ask Ben and me either.
迈克:要是我们会为度假开家庭会议,那现在为什么就不能这孩子开个家庭会议?
Mike: Bothered thing is... If we have a family meeting about vacations.Shouldn't we have a talk about this?
开萝尔:你说得对.
Carol: You are right.
迈克:是的,你知道我的意思,我认为爸妈是想把这孩子硬塞给我们.
Mike: Yeah, you know what I think.I think mom and dad try to slip the new kid about.
开萝尔:迈克,
Carol: Mike, we should still have a family meeting.
我们还是开个家庭会议.
We obviously have a lot to discuss.
我敢打赌爸妈也会觉得这是个好提议的,他们本就喜欢和我们交流,
I bet mom and dad will think it's a great idea too.They love to communicate.
我支持开个家庭会议.
I'll be the one who propose it.
麦琪:好吧,这问题就这么解决.晚上孩子要是哭了,那我就起来照顾.
Maggie: Ok, ok, here is the answer about the problem.When the baby cries at night, I'll be one who gets up.
杰森:不不!你要在镜头前要有个好形象.要是你睡眠不足,会看上去很难看的.
Jason: No, no.no... you have a good looking in front of the news camera
If you are sleepy, then look like a dead worm's nover.A Nice dad
麦琪:不,杰森,你的睡眠也很重要,因为你第二天早上还要看病人.
Maggie: But, Jason, you have to get your sleep to your patients every morning.
杰森:是的,要是我早上看上去像个鬼,
Jason: Sure, when I look like hell in the morning,
那我的病人就会感觉好些的!那就是我工作的全部.
my patients feel better about themselves.That is my job.
麦琪:但要是这导致你病人减少怎么办?
Maggie: But what if you resent scaling down your practice.
你会不会怪我和孩子?
What if you resent me, what if you resent baby?
杰森:麦琪?
Jason: Maggie?
迈克:爸爸妈妈,我们想要马上开个家庭会,
Mike: Mom and Dad, we need a Seavor's family meeting right now.
我在为我们家的前途担心.
I fear for the future of this family.
杰森:迈克,我们现在有点忙!
Jason: Mike, we are a little busy.
麦琪:迈克,现在你爸爸很累.
Maggie: Your father is tired, Mike.
开萝尔:爸爸妈妈,我们的确需要马上开个家庭会,
Carol: Mom and Dad, we really need a Seavor's family meeting immediately.
请相信我.
Trust me.
杰森:开萝尔,你妈妈已经和迈克说了现在不行.
Jason: Carol, that's your mother just explained to Mike.
麦琪:当然要开,开萝尔,我们去开吧!
Maggie: Absolutely, Carol.Let's go.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
迈克:什么?爸爸.
Mike: What?Dad?
杰森:你真是伤你妈的心.
Jason: You hurt your mother.
本:起居室,厨房和一间浴,这浴是什么?游泳池,
Ben: Living room, kitchen, one bir.., what's that bir...?
电视机,冰箱,没洗衣房,没了.
Hm, swimming pool, TV, the refrigerator, no laundry.All right.
杰森:把那,你在干什么?
Jason: Ben, what are you doing?
本:找我的卧室.
Ben: Looking for my own place.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
麦琪:宝贝,这是为什么啊?
Maggie: But, sweet heart, why?
本:因为现在我没有卧室了,
Ben: As long as I lost my room,
我必须马上找间像样的卧室.
I might get a room with flowers on the wall.
杰森:好的,那你怎么付你的房租?
Jason: Well, how are you going to pay for this?
本:没问题的.你看,
Ben: No problem.See.
广告上说第一个月是免费的,到时我就租一个月.
Most these ads say the first month rents free, well, I just move every month.
迈克:让我来主持这个家庭会吧!
Mike: I'd like to call a Seavor family Meeting to order?
开萝尔:我想现在谈谈迈克是怎么骗本腾出房间的.
Carol: I moved to talk about how Mike call Ben out of his room.
迈克:开萝尔,你在说谎,我想是你在捣鬼吧!
Mike: Carol, you are not the right fact .I must choose you out at all.
杰森:迈克,你对本做了什么?
Jason: Mike, what did you do to Ben?
迈克:哦,爸爸,这个不是这次问题的目的.我想这次会议我们该谈谈现在的婴儿问题.
Mike: Oh, Dad, It was not the purpose of the meeting.Today I think we
should be talking about how's this baby mass
麦琪:婴儿问题?
Maggie: Baby mass?
开萝尔:迈克,这个婴儿的出生是福事.
Carol: Mike, this baby is a blessed event.
迈克:警察在哪?快把这位女士赶出去.
Mike: Where is Sergeant, Just got this lady out.
开萝尔:爸爸妈妈,迈克讨厌这个婴儿.
Carol: Mom and Dad, Mike hates the baby.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
迈克:不不,是开萝尔挑拨了我和本的关系.
Mike: No no no no.You have confused me and Ben.
杰森:本?
Jason: Ben?
本:我只是想要回我的卧室.
Ben: I just want my room back.
杰森:你是自愿放弃卧室的吗?不是吗?
Jason: Did you volunteer to give up, didn't you?
迈克:现在暂时休会,谢谢.
Mike: This meeting has adjourned.Thank you very much.
麦琪:会议还没完.
Maggie: Here's not.
杰森:迈克,你给我回来.
Jason: Mike, back in here.
麦琪:孩子们,这个即将出生的婴儿会改变这里的一些事,
Maggie: Kids, this new baby is going to change things around here.
有些会变好,有些则刚好相反.
And some of them will be going wonderful, and some of them aren't.
开萝尔:你和本就只为自己着想,
Carol: All you two can think about yourselves.
我个人还是欢迎这孩子说带来的一切变化.
Personally I am looking forward to everything about this baby.
麦琪:每天一下课你就要回来照顾孩子呢?
Maggie: Even coming home straight after school to help out?
开萝尔:当然,那又不是每天都是这样,是吧?
Carol: Of course.This won't be everyday, will it?
麦琪:是的,开萝尔,那你是不是已经准备好更换尿布?
Maggie: No, Carol, you are ready for things like changing dirty diapers?
开萝尔:哦,这我想本会做的.
Carol: Oh, I thought Ben would do that.
本:为什么是我?
Ben: Why me?
开萝尔:因为我的直觉告诉我你最善做这事啦!
Carol: Because my instinct tells me that you would be good at it.
本:你的直觉是对的.
Ben: Instinct is right.
麦琪:开萝尔,更换尿布的事还是由你来做吧!
Maggie: Carol, you should be well doing your share of changing dirty diapers.
迈克:……
Mike: ......
杰森:好吧,
Jason: All right, now,
现在看来我们每个人都得为这孩子做些牺牲.
every member of this family is going to make some sacrifices here.
迈克:我也要吗?
Mike: Me too?
杰森:是,你也要.你必须要适应你的新立体声播放政策.
Jason: Yes, you too.You have to get used to the new stereo policy.
迈克:好吧!没晚十一点我就结束,最晚不会超过凌晨一点.
Mike: Ok, ok, my stereo will be turned off every night by 11 pm.1am tops.
杰森:那可不是我愿望的.
Jason: That's not what we have had in my mind.
迈克:那好吧!那最晚就午夜好了,我保证.
Mike: Ok, midnight, it is you can cam on me.
杰森:我要求不管白天还是黑夜都不要放音乐.
Jason: There will be no music when the baby is sleeping day or night.
迈克:白天和晚上,那还有什么时间放?
Mike: Day or night, what's left?
杰森:本,你愿做什么牺牲?
Jason: Ben, how do you feeling about making sacrifices?
本:我没问题,我可以出去租公寓.
Ben: It's fine of me, I am going to be hanging out on my due plucks.
麦琪:我现在还是不清楚本是怎么失去卧室的.
Maggie: I am still not clear how Ben lost his room.
本:是迈克骗我的.
Ben: Mike counted me out of it.
杰森:这又是个记录, 迈克,我想和你待会在这月光下和你谈谈.
Jason: That's the record show, Mike and I will talk later here in the moon light.
本:我不明白为什么你们一有了孩子,
Ben: Well, what I don't get is why we have to suffer when you are the
我们就得受苦.
one having the baby.
麦琪:本,现在也不是就你们做了牺牲,你爸爸也重新调整了他的工作.
Maggie: Ben, you kids are dealing not the ones to make sacrifices.Here your father can rearrange his whole practice.
杰森:还有你妈妈得暂时离开已经慢慢适应的工作.
Jason: Your mother has to take time off her job she is just getting used to.
本:行了,既然这个孩子已经影响了大家的生活,那你又要生下来呢?
Ben: Well.If this baby is messing everybody up, why are you having it?
麦琪:为什么?
Maggie: Why?
迈克:是的,为什么?
Mike: Yeah, why?
麦琪:好吧,这个问题我不知道怎么回答你们.
Maggie: Well, I never thought about putting it into words.
杰森:是有点困难回答.
Jason: That's not easy to do.
本:那是因为你也不知道.
Ben: That's you don't know either.
麦琪:不不!我们知道.
Maggie: No no no.we know.
我想这个孩子,肯定会给我们带来些曾经有过的奇迹,
I guess because a baby is close to miracle we ever can get to.
就像你们三个出生,
And having each one of you is the most wonderful thing that happened to
在我们眼里,都是一件奇妙的事.
me and your father.
开萝尔:谢谢你,妈妈,你真是太好了,特别你还把迈克加进去了.
Carol: Thank you, mom, that's really beautiful, especially when you include Mike.
迈克:开萝尔.
Mike: Carol.
麦琪:本,这个答案你满意吗?
Maggie: Does that answer your question, Ben?
本:不!
Ben: No
麦琪:不?杰森.
Maggie: No?Jason.
杰森:本,
Jason: Ben, your mother and I we believe nothing in the world is more
我和你妈是认为世界上没有什么比家更重要的啦!
important than our family.
麦琪:是的,我们也可以不管工作和失眠.
Maggie: We sure do.Not work.We are losing sleep,
杰森:也许我的病人数量也会减少一些.
Jason: Maybe I reduce my patients low?
麦琪:不会的.
Maggie: Nothing.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,我们怎么不到楼上去/
Maggie: Oh, honey, why don't we come up all the substances?
杰森:我不知道.
Jason: I don't know.
麦琪:哦,这孩子一定很棒.
Maggie: Oh, this baby is going to be great.
本:你还是没有回答我的问题.
Ben: That doesn't answer my question either.
迈克:我想本的问题是有了这个孩子后,
Mike: I think what Ben is trying to ask here is what's in this baby deal
我们的地位会怎么样?
for us.
杰森:你们的地位?
Jason: What's in it for you?
迈克:这是本的问题.
Mike: It was Ben's question.
麦琪:大家都是公平对待.
Maggie: Well, everything.
杰森:一切都会照旧的.虽然我看到你们平时有太多的吵闹,
Jason: Anything for us.
不过我想实际上你们相互之间是非常爱护的.开萝尔,
You guys insult each other more than anybody I know,
如果没有迈克,
but I also bet my shoulder deep down on earth all that each of you lover
你会怎样?本,
each other Oh, Carol, how would you really feel if there is no Mike?Er?
如果没有开萝尔,你会怎样?
Well, Ben, how would you really feel if there is no Carol?Er?
迈克,你又会怎么样?
Mike, how would you really feel...
现在就保持沉默,不要去破坏这感人的场面.
don't say one word to destroy the sensational scene.
麦琪:想想我们马上就有了一位可爱的新成员了,要是这样,到时我们的生活会更加幸福的.
Maggie: Just think, we are all going to have a new person to love.Once she or he is here, we wonder how we ever lived without her or him.
杰森:本,这个答案你满意吗?
Jason: Ben, does that answer your question?
本:我想是的.那你的意思是不光是妈妈怀孕了,我们也怀孕了,对吗?
Ben: I think so.So you are saying, it's not you and mom are having
a baby.We all pregnant
杰森:哦,本,你讲的太对啦!
Jason: Oh, you couldn't be more right.Ben.
开萝尔:这真是感人,迈克,你是不是也感动得哭了?
Carol: This is so sweet.Mike, you crying too?
迈克:不,这是你的专利.
Mike: No, it's your fee.Oh.
杰森:哦,麦琪,我真是为这些孩子们骄傲.
Jason: Oh, Maggie, I cannot remember where I was more proud of those guys.
麦琪:他们终于为这个即将来临的孩子而激动了,你真是有办法.
Maggie: They are finally truly excited about the baby.And you were wonderful.
杰森:是的!亲爱的,这时候你还在给谁打电话?
Jason: Yeah, yeah, yeah, Honey, who are you calling at this hour?
麦琪:哦,我的医生,我想是时候了.
Maggie: Oh, my doctor.it's time.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:我在开玩笑!
Maggie: Just kidding.
麦琪:是我的老板.
Maggie: My boss.
杰森:为什么不明天再打?
麦琪:我不想再拖了.你好,我是麦琪!我想告诉你我怀孕了,有4个月了,不过要是下星期还让我穿紧身衣,我照干.什么?这不是55512548?
Jason: Why don't call him tomorrow? Maggie: I don't put this off for another.Hello
this is Maggie.Hello.I'm calling to tell you I am pregnant.I am 4 months
long.But if you still want me to put on my leotard next week, I
am game.What?This isn't